

# Su Myat Hnin

UI/UX & Product Designer

- sumyathnin.2017u@gmail.com
- +959959666577
- sumyathnin.github.io
- Kyimyindaing Township, Yangon

### ABOUT ME

I'm a UI/UX and product designer with 4+ years of experience and specilization in mobile and web applications. I love to create a minimalist design of both mobile and web applications. I enjoy creating business card images, line art and graphic design images as well. I would like to talk with people, who is interested in design strategy, about creating user-centered design that intends for everyone easier to make accessible, understand and utilize.

#### EDUCATION

#### **University Of Information Technology**

B.C.SC. Software Engineerning

🛗 2014 - 2019 • Yangon, Myanmar

# CERTIFICATION

## **Google UX Design Professional Certificate**

**Google** 

## **Professional UI/UX Design Course**

**UAcademy** (Future Now)

### **Graphic Design Course**

**BGV** Institute

#### **Embedded Interface Design Specialization**

University of Colorado Boulder

## VOLUNTEERING & WORKSHOP

Visual Designing in UXMM

UX Design Workshop by CuriousCore

Mobile App Prototype (UI Design) by Beetroot

## MY DESIGN

https://www.behance.net/sumyathnin

https://dribbble.com/SU12345

### SKILL

#### **Strategy**

Web Design Mock-up

Mobile Design Wireframing

Graphic Design Prototyping

#### **Product Design Tools**

Adobe XD Figma

Adobe Photoshop Invision

Adobe Illustrator Miro

Sketch Balsamiq

### EXPERIENCE

#### **Venus Lab**

Ct, 2021 - Current

#### **Piyawasa**

Feb, 2021 - Oct, 2021

#### **Royal Majestic - Travels and Tours**

Mov, 2019 - Jan, 2021

## LANGUAGE

Myanmar (Mother tongue)
English (Upper Intermediate)

# Honorable Projects

#### **MyanmarAPN Mobile Application**

Venus Lab

#### LivePlaza Website

Preelance

#### Olivego Mobile Application

Venus Lab